A NASA satellite orbiting over Portugal took photographs that reveal the of from
ships. One of the photos shows a thin film of clouds above the brilliant blue of the
North Atlantic, cut by white lines of thicker clouds that look like scars.
One of the photos shows a thin film of clouds above the brilliant blue of the North
Atlantic, cut by white lines of thicker clouds that look like scars.
NASA officials explained those thicker clouds are signs of ship traffic below.
When ships power their way through the ocean, they pump exhaust into the atmosphere,
just as cars do.
NASA officials explained those thicker clouds are signs of ship traffic below.
When ships power their way through the ocean, they pump exhaust into the atmosphere,
just as cars do.
And those massive amounts of particles can cause clouds to form.
Hit enough of those particles in one place as from the exhaust of a ship, and they
can lead to the creation of new clouds easily visible from space.
These clouds can be huge.
Some of them stretch hundreds of kilometers.